# **JOHNNY DUNN**

https://github.com/jddunn/ | https://jddunn.github.io/ | johnnyddunn@gmail.com

Remote

### Summary

Full-stack dev experienced in building machine learning infrastructure and data pipelines, training and deploying custom models, and fine-tuning LLMs. Experienced in web3 / full-cycle smart contract development, MEV bots, and NFT integrations in web and games.

### Professional Experience

**Tilting Point** New York, NY

Senior Blockchain Engineer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

- Acted as blockchain architect to build infrastructure and marketplace backend for NFT and token integrations in mobile games publisher SDK on Polygon / MATIC chain, working with MATIC engineers for best practices.
- Developed ERC-20, ERC-721 smart contracts with custom metadata properties, APIs for managing NFT metadata, and internal airdropping service. Architected secure multisig wallet operations; rescued \$1 million+ from missent transactions.

<u>eBay</u> New York, NY

Software Engineer 2 (Full-Stack)

June 2020 - April 2021

- Worked on REST API in Scala & Spring-Boot to service data asynchronously based on item selections to UI, improving UX.
- Created deployment infrastructure process enabling E2E developer experience for backend / ML teams. Set up Jenkins pipelines to connect underlying UI libraries, SSR backends to serve web data, and APIs returning ads data from ML models.

### Freelance (Grapple Media, Notebrush, Edelman, HAL)

NLP Engineer / Software Engineer / Product Designer (Contract)

November 2018 - Jan 2021

- Created user stories, animated wireframes and functional product demo for Notebrush's MVP.
- Developed web crawling infrastructure with automated pipeline to feed data into training news classifiers and sentiment analysis models for Grapple Media.
- Trained models to create photo filters applying aesthetics of specific films to selfies for Edelman's interactive AI exhibits.
- Developed / sold sentiment analysis model to HAL (HereAfterLegacy), and continued development work to deliver their MVP.

#### **IPSoft** New York, NY

Cognitive Implementation Engineer

June 2017 - December 2017

- Implemented modules for virtual assistant AI Amelia for corporate client-facing solutions following agile practices.
- Improved workflow and productivity by writing data processing scripts to be distributed to internal teams.

# **Projects**

Quire.work - Turn static forms and interviews into conversational experiences powered by LLMs. https://quire.work

2023

Restless - Always-on anti-malware software using malicious language processing (HAN model) techniques. https://github.com/jddunn/restless

2020

Text RPG Engine - ES6 JS library to create text adventures / interactive fiction with custom player interactions.

2020

https://github.com/iddunn/text-rpg-engine

**Dementia progression analysis** - Dementia progression classifier for MRIs using CNN and transfer learning.

https://github.com/jddunn/dementia-progression-analysis

2018

# Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Design and Technology (May 2017) - Parsons School of Design

### Awards

5<sup>th</sup> Place, AT&T National VR and AR Challenge, with THiNKIMMERSIVE team. (http://npe100.com/)

2017

XRC Labs Young Entrepreneurs Residential Program

Spring 2017

# Skills

| <b>Programming Languages</b> | Solidity   Python   Golang   JavaScript   Java   Scala   C#   SQL   HTML   CSS   SCSS                   |
|------------------------------|---|
| Frontend                     | React   Next.js   Redux Toolkit (RTK)   ChakraUI   NextUI     Tailwind     D3.js   three.js   Bootstrap |
| Backend                      | ethers.js   HardHat   LangChain   Hugging Face   OpenAl   FastAPI   Django   Tornado   Keras            |
|                              | TensorFlow   PyTorch   OpenCV   spaCy   CoreNLP   NumPy   SciPy   pandas   scikit-learn   Celery        |
|                              | Scrapy   BS4   Selenium   Flashbots   Geth   Gnosis Safe  |
| Databases                    | MySQL   Postgres   Prisma   SQLAlchemy   MongoDB   GraphQL   Hadoop   Elasticsearch   Redis             |
| DevOps                       | AWS (EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, Amplify, RedShift)   Docker   Kubernetes   Jenkins                         |
|                              | Unity   Git   Postman   Linux   Burp Suite   Adobe Creative Suite   Processing   openFrameworks         |
| Tools / Software / Other     | SketchUp   PyCharm   IntelliJ   Visual Studio   PWAs   Electron   Capacitor   Android Studio            |